<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><item><title>resume experiments: skills-first vs chronology</title><link>https://nikopastore.github.io/cf-autopost-feed/</link><guid>cbe95f0f-0cc1-4e3c-ba2f-841c690182ec</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:21:37 GMT</pubDate><description>In the evolving landscape of job applications, experimenting with resume formats can make a significant difference. A skills-first resume emphasizes your abilities and achievements, making it ideal for showcasing transferable skills, especially for those changing careers or entering the workforce. On the other hand, a chronological resume highlights your work history, providing a clear timeline of your professional journey. Which format do you think resonates more with employers today, and have you tried either approach in your job search? — CF 20251012-0021-3D46 #jobsearch #careeradvice #jobmarket</description></item><item><title>AI’s impact on hiring and job design</title><link>https://nikopastore.github.io/cf-autopost-feed/</link><guid>6b8116e0-fb8e-43d2-9361-217cd9ff274b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:22:18 GMT</pubDate><description>AI is revolutionizing hiring and job design by streamlining processes, enhancing candidate matching, and enabling data-driven decision-making. With AI tools, companies can analyze vast amounts of candidate data, reducing bias and improving diversity in hiring. This technology also allows for the creation of more dynamic job roles that adapt to the evolving needs of the business and workforce. As we embrace these advancements, what are your thoughts on the balance between human intuition and AI in shaping the future of work? — CF 20251011-2322-3AF2 #AI #Hiring #JobDesign #FutureOfWork #CareerDevelopment</description></item><item><title>how Gen Z reshapes the workplace</title><link>https://nikopastore.github.io/cf-autopost-feed/</link><guid>868862eb-faa3-4181-b727-ce3796a10b88</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 22:42:20 GMT</pubDate><description>Gen Z is transforming the workplace with their unique values and expectations. This generation prioritizes work-life balance, inclusivity, and purpose-driven careers, pushing employers to adapt their cultures and policies. They embrace technology and flexibility, advocating for remote work options and digital collaboration tools. As they enter the workforce, organizations are recognizing the need for mentorship and continuous learning opportunities to foster growth. How do you see Gen Z's influence shaping your workplace environment? — CF 20251011-2242-8228 #GenZ #workplaceculture #futureofwork</description></item><title>Career Forge Autopost Feed</title><link>https://nikopastore.github.io/cf-autopost-feed/</link><description>Auto-generated career content</description></channel></rss>